Once upon a time, there was a maiden in love.
I want to tell my beloved how I feel,
but my love might be over the moment I confess it.
Every day she suffered, agonizing in this way.
She took no meals, and even sleep evaded her.
Eventually she died,
without ever having been able to communicate her feelings.
But the man she loved married another woman,
and lived happily ever after,
without even the slightest inkling that she had ever existed.
what oh i fell asleep while i was still a duck in fakir's arms i wonder if fakir abandoned this
for me what they're stopped congratulations little duck
the sense of pride has returned to the prince
all the wandering shards of the prince's heart have returned now what really so right now he's
yes he must be enjoying some excruciating misery right about now because the dear praying prince
doesn't quite have all of the heart shards back yet but you just said they'd all returned
mr drosselmeyer oh the wandering shards hidden inside sinks in other people's hearts but
unfortunately those aren't all the shards really of course his heart has to keep the raven from
moving after all that is why it was shattered oh i've no time for this wait come back what should
i do then where's the rest of his heart the prince's heart is being dyed in raven's blood can i put it
back to normal can't you tell me bye bye little doc we'll have the opportunity to meet again when i feel
what's that you say you met drosselmeyer yeah it looks like whenever i meet drosselmeyer time somehow
stops you can come in now and then he said the rest of the heart shards were sealing away the raven
and also that the heart shards i returned to muto are causing him a lot of pain so what of it
if drosselmeyer is right that moment when all the heart shards are returned we'll see the raven's
resurrection in other words the start of the battle muto must be prepared for some suffering already
if you aren't prepared to handle that as well you should stop being princess tutu
i'll protect muto with my sword i wish you weren't always going around swinging swords and stuff i mean
it's really dangerous you know so you're saying i'm incapable as a knight is that what you think
that's not it you've spent all your time reading up on this and stuff right i just thought this kind
of night well probably wouldn't be um fuck here if your wounds have healed go home i'll walk you
um are you mad no not particularly you are mad
thank you very much for the bandage later good night a prince who can't even protect a princess
you're a knight who couldn't even find the strength to die
what can you do the story no longer has need of you does that mean the story will stay exactly
the same regardless of whether i'm here or not
fakir was acting weird getting mad and then suddenly depressed
why haven't you watch out you are just nearly centimeters from mary mr cat
oh well thanks you were all spaced out thinking about fakir weren't you
no i
i had a feeling that this might happen so i have a love letter to fakir prepare if you wander around
school carrying something like that miss bottom is bound to come so ask her to pass it on for you
miss bottom she goes and delivers love letters for people word is she knows the feelings of people in
love she knows their feelings we'll call it the great lovey dovey letter operation
uh well best of luck to you come on we have to prepare to cover her later
a love letter to fakir if i gave him this he'd say don't waste time on trifles idiot or something kind
of like that oh is that it zura lovey dovey zura although if she knows feelings i wonder if it would be
possible for me to tell how muto truly feels if i could have that same power miss bottom
my prince aren't you here my prince what is this it looks as if he fought with someone
could it be is this newest heart chart affecting him so violently
i must overcome this raven's blood in me and uphold my pride as a prince
i wonder what kind of person miss bottom is
are you agonizing over your love are you miss bottom
i'm bottom friend of all those who are in love so where's your letter
your tail is not a tail zora where's your tail zora
oh miss bottom oh donkey donkey lovey dovey donkey miss bottom miss bottom
oh no you've got it all wrong i'm not bottom or anybody has to do with love letters and
oh aren't you that upperclassman i see around you found me out anyway i'm hermia please don't tell
anyone okay i'll make sure your letter gets delivered no that's okay my friend was the one who wrote it for
me but she's kind of got the wrong idea about which person i like so oh by the way i'm duck
miss duck huh well when you've written your real letter bring it to me any time okay oh
i would but circumstances keep me from confessing my love i see um miss hermia do you know people's
feelings what oh i don't know but sometimes i can sense them like ah this person is in love
or she looks lonely maybe she's suffering from a broken heart i'm fairly tall you know so i'm
always the one furthest to the back of the core but one day i noticed i could see the feeling of
being in love written on everyone's backs the heart-rending feelings of people in love love is a
wonderful thing but it also makes people suffer and be sad right so everyone has a hard time saying i
love you and they're all keeping their feelings inside i thought i'd at least like to try and see
if there was something i could do to help those people i see but you know lately it's all been
letters written to myuto written to myuto yes i bring him lots of letters every day most are from
people whose feelings ultimately won't be returned though i guess you must see myuto pretty much every day
then huh miss hermia yes well actually the odd thing is myuto usually comes to me so then you
know something about myuto's feelings don't you huh anything is fine i'm sorry myuto's feelings
are the one person's i can't seem to read oh i see oh are you by any chance one of those who likes
myuto too huh oh i guess you must like him too huh miss hermia no no no you've got it all around
i don't have any feelings for myuto i have someone else i like his name is lysander mr lysander
i have to get more hard shards back
crazy
who does the prince's heart belong to and where is the rest of it that is a secret
my prince you needn't suffer anymore your princess is i i will rescue you from your suffering and pain
return prince of the crows return to me
i will not become the prince of the crows
if you resist your suffering will just continue i can handle suffering you have raven's blood running
through your veins just like i do no one can erase it no one can stop it
i will love you more deeply than anyone else can i'll give you my love
you'll give me your love how kind it's good to know your love seeks its natural object princess
yes you ought to love me more you ought to love me more me alone
prince
not enough not enough
not enough love
shut up
see lysander is someone in my grade from the sculpture division this is one of his works wow
your heart gets warm just looking at it doesn't it huh yeah it's as if the sculpture is somehow
filled with the warm and tender feeling of love right he must have been thinking about someone while
while he created it it might have been you miss hermia no definitely not i know myself better than
anyone else does so
is that mr lysander yeah doesn't he exude kindness uh sure
it's the mime for do you mean me what's that mime supposed to mean
the the mime for marriage don't know that one the mime for vow oh the mime for no
that was a close call yeah huh why don't you write a love letter
what's that sound oh something important's come up that is goodbye
what are you doing playing with uzo would you mind being a little quieter up there sorry
oh fuck here researching in books again huh i'm just doing what i can however small
i haven't cast off my sword oh right come on uzura we're in the way so let's go
how many times must i tell you why why am i so obsessed with books
no matter what book i open though they've all had the endings torn out
the ghost knight's book was the same but i saw the end of that book in my dreams
damn it what does this mean we have to be quiet in the library that underdeveloped hermia of all
people i can't believe she's with muto oh this is our vaccine huh um excuse me did something happen
with muto and miss hermia something she said they're on a date holding hands and going towards the
grove behind the school behind the school what a shop you want to dig too oh no that's okay thank you very much
hermia or perhaps should i say bottom the donkey did you know i was bottom the donkey all along
you're the only one i've been looking at all this time
i know everything the fact that you like lysander included i'm here these are today's letters that
rubbish you are my princess you are mine and mine alone hermia you don't have the courage to confess
your own love you're delivering other people's letters just to fool yourself you're wrong that's not
what you make it look like goodwill but it's all for yourself let's be honest but you know that's
fine because everybody else is just using you too you might as well focus exclusively on yourself from
now on if you love me you won't have to fool yourself anymore love only me and hate everyone else
yes yes i will love only you muto and i will hate everyone else from now on then as proof
you'll give me your beautiful heart won't you i will then come dance into my arms and give me your heart
moment if i have you i can become a prima ballerina can't i i'm sick of being the go-between for other
people i will act for my own sake for a muto's sake yes come and sacrifice your life for my sake
miss hermia
miss hermia don't go over there
are you going to interfere please come and dance with me miss hermia dance with you hermia hurry and
come come here give me your love now i demand it yes i'm coming
good my loyal maid here come into my arms miss hermia is that really all right is it all right to end
your love without ever having said anything it's fine you can just throw away a meaningless love like that
yes yes such a love should be cast aside that's not true it isn't meaningless it's a precious feeling of
yours miss hermia it is still love whether you speak it or not but if that truly is a precious feeling it
would only be cruelty to throw it away i don't want you to hide that feeling on your back i want you to tell him
about it
if i were allowed i would also if i were only allowed
be gone be gone from inside me raven yes that's right i haven't i haven't told lysander anything about
this yet about my feelings yes
the feeling that has grown to the bursting point inside you that is real love that's right what
you're seeking is false love it's counterfeit love shut up what is this real love if the love i'm seeking
is false love then all the love in the world must be false
miss hermia
lysander
i just saw ducks loving dubbing zura
yes
well lysander i you must be surprised at me saying this out of the blue but you see well i
lysander i wanted to say
i love you
could that be
i made you my model without asking because i thought i'd confess my love to you once i'd finish it
oh
hey
what
uzra brought this to me
i i didn't write it pk and lilye wrote it so what should i say um i'm sorry
don't waste time on trifles
this idiot
i knew it
real love is it don't make me laugh everyone just wants to be loved that's all
my poor dear prince
don't worry i'm positive father's blood will save you from your suffering quite soon
that's right we have to find a sacrifice of course for our own sakes too
this isn't this isn't for you i'm going to feed the foolish raven a meal that's all
as a small token of my gratitude for helping to awaken me that's right this is the story of the
prince and the raven isn't it the fight began long long ago but their age-old enmity is still
fresh you haven't forgotten that now have you dear little duck
Is she defending the bitingly sarcastic, fantastic Fakir?
An older woman lover, huh?
The stories that boy used to write now and again, sometimes they came true.
I'll protect Mewtwo as a knight. End of story. I won't take orders from you.
And it was starting to look like we'd be able to work together, too. I don't like this.
Mewtwo, I will not allow you to harm Retzel.
Stop! The two of you fighting! It's not going to...
You know you can't lay a finger on me, Fakir.
Oh, you children who love stories, come gather round.
Thank you.